He's got a lot on his mind.
Greenberg is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Noah Baumbach.
Roger Greenberg, a failed musician now making a living as a carpenter in New
York, returns to Los Angeles to house-sit for his brother.
He's stranded there—since he doesn't drive—until his
brother's assistant, Florence, comes to his rescue.
She's as much a lost soul as he is, and the pair form a significant
connection—giving Roger a much-needed reason to be happy.
Roger Greenberg, played by Ben Stiller.
Florence Marr, played by Greta Gerwig.
Ivan Schrank, played by Rhys Ifans.
Beth (Beller's Party), played by Jennifer Jason Leigh.
Eric Beller (Beller's Party), played by Mark Duplass.
Gina, played by Merritt Wever.
Greenberg is a 2010 American romantic comedy-drama film directed by Noah Baumbach, who wrote
the screenplay and co-wrote the story with his then-wife Jennifer Jason Leigh.
The film stars Ben Stiller, Greta Gerwig, Rhys Ifans, and Leigh, with Mark Duplass, Merritt Wever, Chris
Messina, Brie Larson, Juno Temple, Jake Paltrow, and Dave Franco in supporting roles.
The film's soundtrack features the first film score by James Murphy.
The film had its world premiere at the 60th Berlin
International Film Festival on February 14, 2010.
Distributed by Focus Features, Greenberg began a limited theatrical release in New York City and Los
Angeles on March 19, 2010, followed by a wide release in the United States on March 26.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed $7
million worldwide against a budget of $25 million.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.